Acknowledge that your heart is the prayer room.
My heart is the prayer room.
Lord, speak to my heart; let me hear Your voice.
Right now, begin to acknowledge this - speak to my heart; let me hear Your voice.
My heart is the prayer room.
Lord, speak to my heart; let me hear Your voice.
Open your lips right now; you have to prepare your heart.
My heart is the prayer room.
Lord, speak to my heart; let me hear Your voice.
Viewers all over the world, wherever you are right now, acknowlege your heart is the prayer room.
Ask God to speak to your heart. You want to hear Him; you want to hear His voice.
Whatever mountain you are facing is darkness.
Sickness, disease, afflication and setback are darkness.
Whatever giving you headaches, trouble, setback and limitation is darkness.
Right now, begin to acknowledge this - I will never forget who is Light when I come out darkness.
Open your lips and confess this - I will never forget who is Light when I come out from darkness.
Prayer: I will never forget who is Light when I come out from darkness.
Limitation is darkness; affliction is darkness; disease is darkness.
Viewers all over the world, I will never forget who is Light when I come out of darkness.
Open your lips and confess this.
I will never forget who is Light when I come out of darkness.
Disease, affliction, failure, disappointment and limitation are darkness.
That mountain of yours is darkness.
I will never forget who is Light when I come out of darkness.
Open your lips and confess this; prepare yourself.
You are the Deliverer. You are the Healer of wounds inside and outside; hear my voice.
Open your lips.
Lord, heal their brokenness, in Jesus Christ's name we pray.
You have acknowledged that sickness, disease and whatever challenges you are having are darkness.
I command you to come out of darkness, in the name of Jesus!
Come out of darkness!
That disease, that affliction - come out!
Open your lips. Begin to come out of darkness, so that you can acknowledge the light.
Come out of darkness and acknowledge the light!
You demon, I command you right now!
You infirmity, I command you to come out of darkness!
In the name of Jesus!
Because of the confessional statement you made from the beginning, you don't need much strength.
Already, you have confessed that you will acknowledge the light
when you come out of darkness.
Right now, I command that darkness to come out!
You infirmity, you evil spirit, come out! Come out of darkness!
I say, come out of darkness!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
In the name of Jesus!
Listen to me. You have acknowledged that you will never forget who is Light
when you come out of darkness.
Every darkness around!
Prayer!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I want to kill him!
- Who are you?
- I'm a demon.
How did you destroy him? What have you done to him, his marriage?
This guy tries; I want to kill him.
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Can you follow me with your prayer room?
Your heart is your prayer room.
I want you to follow me with your prayer room.
Right now, I want to speak to your life!
Lord Jesus, heal their brokenness!
Be healed! Be delivered!
Every darkness around you!
Can you repeat this word:
Every darkness around me, be dispelled!
Prayer!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
I'm an ancient spirit!
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Hallelujah.
I live in the family.
Who wants to do well in the family?
What have you done to this lady?
In her family, nobody, no female has to marry.
What have you done to her marriage?
Who wants to be rich? Haha! I'm alive!
How did you enter her?
I live in the family - as soon as you are born.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
You are the Healer. Heal my wounds inside and outside.
Prayer!
You are the Healer. Lord Jesus, heal my wounds outside and inside.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I want to kill her family!
I don't want her to get married!
I don't want her to marry at all!
She refused to marry me. She ran away.
I'm the spiritual husband.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
What have you done to her family?
I gave her the spirit of epilepsy so that she will not get married at all.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Say, You are the Healer.
Heal my wounds inside and outside!
Prayer!
Vomiting Blood & Poisonous Substances
Let me go!
I have destroyed her!
She cannot get married!
She cannot do anything!
I'm her husband!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Spiritual husband!
I have destroyed her!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Say, Lord Jesus, heal my brokenness! Prayer!
Spiritual husband!
- What have you done to this lady?
- I have destroyed her.
She's not happy.
What have you done to her marriage?
She's not happy in her marriage.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Heal my brokenness, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Right now, you want to hear the voice of the Lord.
At the command of Jesus, Peter walked on the sea.
At the command of Jesus, blind Bartimaeus regained his sight.
I command every affliction, every darkness in your life -
I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
I command them out so that you can hold your faith.
Say, Lord Jesus, heal me so that I can hold my faith, in Jesus' name.
Say, heal me, Lord, so that I can hold my faith!
Deliver me, Lord! Set me free, Lord, so that I can hold my faith!
In Jesus' name! I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Every darkness in your life, demon, familiar spirit, limitation in progress!
In the name of Jesus!
Let there be light!
Right now, begin to acknowledge the light.
I was dark; You brought me into the light.
Confess it: I was dark; You brought me into the light.
Thank You, Jesus!
Confess.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Viewers all over the world, the Spirit of God has a package for you.
Every darkness - inside, outside - I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Remember, disease is darkness. Affliction is darkness. Limitation in progress is darkness.
Your need right now, in the name of Jesus, be restored!
Be restored!
Yes.
I know you have acknowledged light; you will never forget who is Light.
I command every darkness around you, around your business, career, family and finances,
right now, I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Go, in the name of Jesus!
Let there be light!
I can hear, "Let there be light", in the name of Jesus Christ!
I restore you back to glory!
I restore you back, in the name of Jesus!
Be restored so that you can hold your faith!
Be healed so that you can hold your faith!
Be delivered so that you can hold your faith!
Thank You, Lord!
Rejoice!
Right now, your confession - I was dark; You brought me into the light.
I was dark; You brought me into light.
Your confession.
Viewers all over the world, your confession right now: I was dark; You brought me into the light.
I will never forget who is Light when I come out of darkness.
I was dark; You brought me into the light.
Glory be to God!
I can hear! Rejoice!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Give glory to God!
Give thanks to God. Give thanks to Him.
You can hold your faith now. Say, I can hold my faith.
Now, I came out of the darkness, I can hold my faith.
Right now, give thanks to God.
Give thanks to Him.
Give thanks to God.
The Lord is good all the time.
Put your nation in the hands of God.
Ask God to protect your nation, for peace and to redeem the leaders and people of your nation.
Ask God for protection; ask God to redeem your country.
Pray for your nation, for God's intervention and protection.
In Jesus Christ's name we pray!
I can't hear you.
[Amen!]
Right now, remember your people at home.
I know you are here for someone who is sick.
Whoever he is and whatever situation they are in, lift up your voice in prayer.
Ask God to restore the situation, restore the person, restore your loved one.
Glory! Prayer!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Right now, you can begin to confess whom you are.
I was dark; You brought me into the light.
Confession. Confess whom you are.
You are my Healer, my Deliverer.
Old things pass away; all things become new.
Now, I can hold my faith.
You have healed my brokenness.
You have healed me inside and outside.
Thank You, Lord, in Jesus Christ's name.
If you are just coming in at this moment, lift your voice with me.
If you are coming to Jesus for the first time in your life, I want to pray with you anywhere you are.
Lord Jesus, come into my heart.
I want to hear Your voice; let me hear Your voice.
Let me hear what to do; let me hear where to go; let me hear how to do them.
In Jesus Christ's name.
Give glory to God; give thanks to God.
TT: Mel Flowers 22/04/2019